var questionBank = [
    {
        question: "Common data types DO Not Include:",
        choices: ["numbers", "booleans", "strings", "alerts"],
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Arrays in Javascript can be used to store __________.",
        choices: ["numbers", "booleans", "strings", "all of the above"],
        ans: 3,
    },

    {
        question: "How do you call a function named 'myFunction'?",
        choices: [
            "call function myFunction()",
            "myFunction()",
            "call myFunction()",
            "call.myFunction()",
        ],
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct way to declare an array in JavaScript?",
        choices: [
            "var colors = 'red', 'green', 'blue';",
            "var colors = ['red', 'green', 'blue'];",
            "var colors = (1:'red', 2:'green', 3:'blue');",
            "var colors = 1 = ('red'), 2 = ('green'), 3 = ('blue');",
        ],
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What operator is the AND operator?",
        choices: [
            "&",
            "+",
            "&&",
            "||"],
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What type of event occurs when an HTML element is clicked on?",
        choices: [
            "onchange",
            "onmouseclick",
            "onmouseover",
            "onclick"],
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "How do you write a comment in JavaScript?",
        choices: [
            "this is a comment",
            "<!-- this is a comment -->",
            "/*this is a comment*/",
            "//this is a comment",
        ],
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed within______? ",
        choices: [
            "quotes",
            "curly brackets",
            "parentheses",
            "square brackets"
        ],
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "String value must be enclosed within______ When being assigned to variables. ",
        choices: [
            "quotes",
            "parenthesis",
            "curly brackets",
            "commas"
        ],
        ans: 2,
    },

    {
        question: "A veryuseful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
        choices: [
            "for loops",
            "JavaScript",
            "console.log",
            "terminal/bash"
        ],
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "The acronym for the object representation of a webpage, DOM, stands for:",
        choices: [
            "Digital Orientation Method",
            "Doorway Opening Mechanism",
            "Document Object Model",
            "Device Operation Manual",
        ],
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "The starting index value for an array in JavaScript is ______ :",
        choices: [
            "null",
            "void",
            "0",
            "1"
        ],
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
        choices: [
            "JavaScript",
            "terminal/ bash",
            "for loops",
            "console log"],
        ans: 3,
    },
];